Inventory to the John Nicholas Beffel Papers TAM.055
Tamiment Library / Wagner Archives
- Series III: Writings by Beffel
  - Contains: (Box 15)
    "Stephen Crane Gets Fired": Includes copies of the article, letters to and from Edgar Snyder, notes by JNB for article and related misc. material
    "Wolheim, Master Teller of Tales": Includes draft of article, notes and questionnaires pertaining to the article; Miscellaneous Writings.
  - Contains: (Box 16)
    American Mosaic; Light and Shadow on the Land of the Free: An outline and proposal for a book on Americana to be written by Beffel. Many of the tentative chapters have been written or published as short stories
    "Book of Light": Seems to be a diary of sorts; Julv 14, 1926 December 24, 1939
    Corn Belt Bov: A series of sketches based on Beffel's early years in Seneca, Illinois. They were intended to be part of an autobiography (?). It is believed that some of the sketches were published as separate short stories. It is alternately entitled "Honest Hearts and Willing Hands"
    Desperate Pageantrv: The saga of the Polaris Disaster. This is chapter 1 of a book never written (?)
    Jim Higgins Jail: A partial novel. 115 p.
    Land of the Free: A magazine edited and published by Beffel. It was intended as "A monthly journal which lets in light and air." (never published?)
    Living Men: Devoted to the Struggles of the Driven. A magazine edited and published by Beffel. (See Also map case for an unused design of the cover). It contained articles by various people including David Karsner, Theodore Dreiser and Robert Monov.
    Holdings: Vol. 1 No. 5 (incomplete); Chicago, October 1917, Vol. 2 No. 3,Chicago, February 1913; Vol. 2 No. 3 Chicago, June 1919; Vol. 2 No. 4, New York, October 1919
    The Wart: An incomplete story
    Where Did these Gentlemen Die?”: Manuscript for a proposed book by Beffel which dealt with the mysterious deaths of various distinguished men.
  - Contains: (Box 17)
    Billington and Colonial Families:
    Notes and manuscripts relating to John Billington, a Pilgrim who was hanged in the Plymouth Colony ten years after its founding, and to early colonial times. Also includes a small part of a manuscript by George Prince. The proposed title of Beffel's book, in 1930, was "John Billington: Pilgrim to the Gallows."
  - Contains: (Box 18)
    Anecdotes
    Articles and Essays (2 folders), Some published: A—M, M—Z
    Book Reviews
    Letters to the Editor
    News Items and Releases (some published):
    News Items and Releases: Contains five articles for the Federated Press on marine workers, 1921
    Newspaper and Magazine Writings: Approximately 60 articles clipped from magazines and newspapers written by Beffel (Some of the articles can be found in manuscript form in the folders labeled “Articles and essays,” and “Short stories”)
    Notes and Memorandums
    Poems (some published)
    Collected Poems: poems by various authors, clipped and copied by Beffel
    About JNB: includes biographical notes on Beffel and 11 photos
    Miscellaneous Material.
  - "Series" VIII: Index to Correspondents (alphabetical)
    Scope and Content Note
    ABBATE, Dr. Frank: See: Tresca Memorial Committee Nos. 3 and 5 (Subject Section) // ABRAMSON, Herman, See: Morley, Christopher // ADDIE (Farrar Andre ?) // AHLQUIST, Mary, See: HOPE, Mary // ALBERT // ALBERT, Ruth // ALDECOA; Dr. Carmen (Malo): See: League for Mutual Aid Anniversary Dinner (Subject Section) // ALICE // ALLER, L. E., See: Centralia Correspondence No. 2 (Subject Section) // ALVANO, Vincenzo, See: Tresca Memorial Committee No. 2 (Subject Section) // ANDE // ANDREWS, Louise // ANGELL, Ernest, See: League for Mutual Aid 1940s (Subject Section) // *APPEL, Paul // AULICINO, Armand // AURAND, A. M. (Jr.) // AXELROD, Sally, See: Ferrer School (Subject Section)
    B ?, Louis // BAILEY, Forrest (including a letter from Dana College 1933, about a Forrest Bailey Collection) // BALABANOFF, Angelica, See Also: Felicani, Aldino; Tresca Memorial Committee No. 2 (Subject Section) // BALDWIN, Roger, See Also the following Subject Sections: Centralia Correspondence, League for Mutual Aid 1940s, Sacco and Vanzetti Correspondence No. 3, Memorial Issue of Controcorrente General Correspondence // BALLARD, S. J. // BARNETT, Mrs. Eugene, See: Centralia Correspondence No. 2 (Subject Section) // BARRY, Dick // BASS, Dr. Elizabeth // BAXTER, Lydia M. // BEA // BEARDSLEY, Helen Marston // BEARDSLEY, John // BECKER, Ray, See: Centralia Correspondence No. 1 (Subject Section); BELL, Daniel // BELLOC, H. (Hillaire) // BENNET, Isadora // BERLIN (From Ester Fay, secretary to Mr. Berlin) // BERNAYS, Hella // BERTILLE, Sister Mary // BETTER, F. R., See: League for Mutual Aid 1940s (Subject Section) // BLANKENEHORN, Mrs. // BOHN, Frank, See: Centralia Correspondence No. 2 (Subject Section) // BOOKER // BORTLE // BRANCH, Frank // *BRAZIER, Richard (Dick), Including his poems "Calling Centralia,” “Answer Us Please" and "The Ballad of the Spokane Free Speech Fight"; See Also: FLETCHER, Ben; // BRINI, Beltrando and Muriel // BROOKS, Elizabeth J., See: LONERGAN, Nella and Warren // BROUN, Haywood, See: Sacco and Vanzetti Correspondence No. I (Subject Section) // BROWN, F. A., See: Centralia Correspondence No. 2 (Subject Section) // BROWNE, Jane // *BUCKLEY, John // BUDNEZ, Louis, See Also: Re: Writing (Subject Section) // BUNCHE, Dr. Ralph J. // BURKE, Evelyn, See: McSwigon, Marie // BURKE, Thomas // *BURR, Jane // BURY, Richard A. // BYER, Samuel, See: Sacco and Vanzetti Correspondence No. 3 (Subject Section)
    CAHN, Edmund // CALESE, Robert (Bob) // CALVERT, Bruce // (+)CAMPBELL, Agnes H. ("Jerry") // CANZANELLI, Beatrice, See: Sacco and Vanzetti Correspondence No. 3 (Subject Section) // CAREL, Jack, See: League for Mutual Aid 1930s (Subject Section) // CAREY; Dr. Eugene F. (Including two manuscripts) // *CARSON, Saul and Betty // *CASCADEN, Gordon Leroy (Including a letter from Norman Thomas) // (+)CHAMBERLAIN, Grace Ann // CELLA, Hon. Alexander J., See: Memorial Issue of Controcorrente General Correspondence (Subject Section) // CHANDLER, Hon. A. B., See: Kentucky Miners No. 1 (Subject Section) // *CHAPLIN, Ralph // CHURCHILL, Mr. // CICCONE, Louis // CLARK, Bennett Champ // CLAYMAN, Clara, See: League for Mutual Aid Anniversary Dinner (Subject Section) // CLEMENT, Travers // CLINTON, Marye, S. // (+)CLINTON, Sackville W. // COLDWELL, Joe (Including a letter to delegates of the Socialist Party Convention, 1948) // COLEMAN?, Arthur, See: Centralia Correspondence No. 2 (Subject Section) // COLEMAN, McAlister (Including two news releases about Coleman) // COLLAT, Ruth // COLLIER, Phyllis // COLLINS, Lillian, See Also: Centralia Correspondence No. 2 (Subject Section) // COLSON, Margaret, See: Centralia Correspondence No. 1 (Subject Section) // *COMFORT, Will Levington // COPPOLA, Sal // COOLIDGE, Hon. Calvin, President of the U.S., See: Centralia Correspondence No. 1 (Subject Section) // COON, Frank B. // COONEY, James P. // CORDER, Minnie Federman // COSTELLO, E. J., See: Federated Press (Subject Section) // COWLEY?, George // CRANE GARTZ, Kate, See: Centralia Correspondence No. 1 (Subject Section) // CRIMMINS, Louise // CROCKER, Donald M. // CROMIE, Robert, See: STARRETT, Vincent // CROSSWAITH, Frank R. // CROUCH, Paul and Tanya, See: Paul Crouch (Writing Section, box 20) // CROY, Homer // CROY, May Savell // CURTIS, Cyrus H. K.
    DALY, Tom // DANNENBERG, Leigh // DAVIDS0N, H. M. // *DAVIN, Tom // DAVIS // DAVIS, Robert H. // DAVIS DUBOIS, Rachel // DAVISON, F. Trubee // DAY // DAY, Dorothy, See Also: Sacco and Vanzetti Correspondence No. 3 (Subject Section) // DEBS, Theodore // DECKER, Ann Folder, See: Sacco and Vanzetti // DE GIOVANNI, Norman Thomas, See Also: Sacco and Vanzetti Correspondence No. 3 (From Donald G. Lothrop) // DEGNAN, Leah C. // DE LEON, Solon // DELL, Floyd // DE SILVER, Margaret, See: Tresca Memorial Committee Nos. 1 4 and 6 (Subject Section) // DERMONDY, Joe // DEUTSCH, Babette, See: Tresca Memorial Committee No. 1 (Subject Section) // DEWART, William T., See: League for Mutual Aid 1930s (Subject Section) // DEWEY, Roberta (Mrs. John) // DIAMOND, Z. N., See: Terzani Case Correspondence (Subject Section) // *DIGGINS, John P. // DI MARCO, Mario (Re: Di Marco Reception Committee anti fascist) // *DILLON, Marv ("Brownie") // DINOWITZER, Lillian Kisluik, See Also: Ferrer School; League for Mutual Aid Anniversary Dinner (Subject Section) // DON // DONAHUE, Ellen // DONALDSON // *DONOVAN, Mary (Hapgood) // DOROTHY // DOS PASSOS, John, See: Sacco and Vanzetti Correspondence No. 1 (Subject Section) // DOUGHERTY, Mary // DOUGLAS, Hon. William 0. // DOWELL // DREIER, Thomas // *DREISER, Theodore // DUNN, Robert W. // DWIR, Tamara.
    E., W. N. // EASLEY, Ralph M., See: League for Mutual Aid 1930s (Subject Section) // EATON, Walter P. // EBERT, Justus // EHRMAN, Herbert B., See Also: Sacco and Vanzetti; Memorial Issue of Controcorrente - General Correspondence (Subject Section) // ELEAZER, Robert B. // *EISENBERG, Daniel (Re: I Find the Missing) // ELLIS, Morris L., See Also: Sacco and Vanzetti Correspondence No. 3 (Subject Section) // ERSKINE, Helen Warder? // EVANS, Ernestine // EVANS, J. L. T., Esq. // EVETT, Robert, See: STARETT, Vincent Re: Review of Starrett book.
    F., L. // FAIRBURN, O. G., See: Centralia Correspondence No. 1 (Subject Section) // FARMER, James // FEINBERG, Harry, See: Centralia Correspondence No. 1 (Subject Section) // *FELICANI, Aldino and Ateo (son), See Also: Controcorrente Memorial Issue Correspondence, Sacco and Vanzetti Correspondence No. 3; Tresca Memorial Correspondence Nos. 1 and 4, Huntington, Catherine (Subject Section) // FELLOWS, Mrs. John // FERGUSON, Fred S. (and from James M. Stefano, secretary for Mr. Ferguson) // FERNWORTH, Lawrence // FIELD, Sara // *FLETCHER, Benjamin H. (relating to) // FLORENTINES // FLYNN, Elizabeth Gurley // FLYNN, Kathryn, See: League for Mutual Aid 1940s (Subject Section) // FORD, Richard, See: Ford and Suhr (Subject Section) // FRAGER, Jack, See: Sacco and Vanzetti Memos, etc. (Subject Section) // FRAENKEL, Osmond K., See: Sacco and Vanzetti Correspondence No. 3 (Subject Section) // FRANK, Adelaide Shulkind, See SHULKIND, Adelaide (Frank) // FRANK, Nelson (From the Nelson Frank Collection) // FRANK, Walter, See: League for Mututal Aid 1960s (Subject Section) // FREIBERG, Bessie // *FRESCO, Mauricio // FRIESE, Louise, See: ZIMMERMAN, Mary // *FUESSLE, Helen // FULLER, Henry B. // *FULLER, Torrey // FULTON, Maude // *Furman, Lee.
    G., Jane? // GAHAN, John A., See Also: Centralia Correspondence No. 2 (Subject Section) // GALLAGHER, Mary E. // GANDHI, Mahatma, See: ROY, Anna // GARCIA LEMA // GARDNER, Hy // GARDINER, D. // GAVIN, Robert, See: Centralia Correspondence No. 1 (Subject Section) // GATES, Frances, See: THOMAS, Norman // *GAWTHORPE, Mary (Sanders) // *GEHRIG, Gladys Bell (including photographs) // GEHRIG, James (with Gehrig, Gladys Bell) // GELBER, Dorothea and Leon // GEORGE // GEORGE, Harrison, See: Centralia Correspondence No. I (Subject Section) // GILDER, Rodman // GILMAN?, Elizabeth, See: Centralia Correspondence No. 1 (Subject Section) // GLICKSTEIN, Ny, See: League for Mutual Aid 1930s (Subject Section) // GOETE?, Ed // GOLDMAN, Emma // GOTTLIEB, Ferd, See: Kentucky 'Miners Folder No. 1 (Subject Section) // GREEN, B. A., See: Centralia Correspondence No. 2 (Subject Section) // GRIFFIN, Elizabeth // GROSSER, Phillys B. // GRUDIN, Louis // GRUENING, Martha, See: League for Mutual Aid (Subject Section) // GUY, Eula.
    *H. (Hodgins?), K. (Katherine?), See Also: Sacco and Vanzetti Correspondence No. 1 (Subject Section) // HAAS, Walter F. (To Donald Harrington) // HAESSLER, Carl // *HALL, Covington ("Covami") HANNA, Rosa Laddon, See: Federated Press (Subject Section) // HANSEN, Harry // HARDMAN, Virginia Mishnun // HAROLD // HARRINGTON, Donald, See: Tresca Memorial Committee No. 2 (Subject Section) // HARRINGTON, Michael // HARRIS, Frank // HAVEL, Nora // HAWKINS?, Carter H. // HAYES, Arthur Garfield (From Theresa H. Saper, secretary to Mr. Hayes), See Also: Terzani Case Correspondence (Subject Section) // HAYWOOD, William B., See: BARRY, Dick; BRAZIER, Richard; BUCKLEY, John; LETCHEM, E.W.; LUNDOFF, John M.; VELEKER, Wilma Haywood // HAZLETT, Dr. William // HEATON, Dennis (Jr.) // HEBER // HENNACY, Ammon, See: League for Mutual Aid Anniversary Dinner (Subject ection) // HENRIETTE // HERTZBERG, Sidney // HEUBSCH, E. W., See: Sacco and Vanzetti Correspondence No. 1; Job and Job hunting (Subject Section) // Hill, Joe, See: THOMPSON, Fred // HILL, Walter // HILLSTROM, Joseph, See, Thompson, Fred // HILSON, Maxine ("Kid") // HODGINS, Katherine H. // HOGAN, Hon. Frank S., See: Tresca Memorial Committee Nos. I and 6 (Subject Section) // HOKE, Calm Morrison (Including a photograph) // HOLCOMBE // HOLLAND, Tom, See: Centralia Correspondence No. 1 (Subject Section) // HOLLOD, Dr. Maurice L., See Also: Ferrer School (Subject Section) // HOPE, Mary (Pseudonym for Mary Ahlquist) // HOPKINS, Arthur // HORNE, Lena // HOWIE, Michael // HUMBLE, Marian? // HUMPHREY, Mary // *HU7NTINGTON, Catherine.
    *INGLIS, Agnes (and Labadie Collection) // ISCA, Valerio, See Also: Sacco and Vanzetti Correspondence No. 3; Memorial Issue of Controcorrente General Correspondence (Subject Section).
    J., Joan // JACK, Gardiner, See: Sacco and Vanzetti Correspondence No. 3; Memorial Issue of Controcorrente General Correspondence (Subject Section) // *JARRETT, Ida // JAY // JARRETT, Agnes // JOHN? // JOHNSON, Oakley // JOHNSTON, Tom, See: Centralia Correspondence No. 2 (Subject Section) // JONES, Joseph Emmett // JOUGHIN, G. Louis // JOYCE, Helen // JULIA.
    KAHN?, Milton // *KARSNER, David // *KARSTEN, Helen Ward Tippy // KATZ, Isadore, See: Terzani Case Correspondence (Subject Section) // KATZENIBACH, Nicholas de B. // *KELLER, Carl, See Also: Centralia Correspondence No. 2; Sacco and Vanzetti Correspondence No. 2 (Subject Section) // KELLER, Helen, See: WALLING, Anna Strunsky // KELLEY, Rosemary // KELLY, Emmett J. // KELLY, Harry, See: Ferrer School // *KENDERDINE, John D. // KENNAN, Ellen A. // KENYON, Hon. Dorothy, See: Sacco and Vanzetti Correspondence No. 3; Tresca Memorial Committee No. 2 (Subject Section) // KIMBALL, Alice Mary // KING, James, See: Centralia Correspondence No. 2 (Subject Section) // KIRCHWAY, George W. // *KITCMN, Inez (Including photographs) // KLINGER, Henry, See: PURCELL, Dorothy // KORBY, Nathan // KNUTSON, Cornelius // KWEI, Teng?
    L., Harry // LAIDLAW, Bill, See Also: Sacco and Vanzetti Correspondence No. 1 (Subject Section) // LAMPMAN, Ben Hur, See: Centralia Correspondence No. 1 (Subject Section) // LANE, C. S., See: Centralia Correspondence No. 1 (Subject Section) // LATCHEM, E. W. // LATHROP, Miss. // LATHROP, Rev. Charles N. // LATTIMER, Ray, See: STARRETT Vincent // LAUT, Agnes C. // LEARNED, Fred // LE GALLIENNE, Hesper // LEGGIT, Deryl // LEHMAN, Max // LEIBOWITZ // LESTER, John // LEVEY, Jeanne // LEVINSON, David // LEWIS, George // LEWIS, Marx // LEWIS, Sinclair // LIGGETT, William Wallace. See Also: League for Mutual Aid 1960s (Subject Section) // LINDHOLM, Harry, See: Centralia Correspondence No. 2 (Subject Section) // LIPPMANN, Walter?, See: Sacco and Vanzetti Correspondence No. 1 (Subject Section) // LONDON, Jack, See: WALLING, Anna Strunsky // *LONERGAN, Nella and Warren, See Also: Box 6 Correspondence // LOPEZ, Frank R. (Pseudonym), See: MARTIN, Alberto // LOCHNER, Louis P. // LOTH, David // LOTHROP, Rev. Donald G., See Also: Sacco and Vanzetti Correspondence Nos. 2 and 3 (Subject Section) // LOUIE // LOVETT?, Robert M. // LOWE, H. Burton // LOWELL, Ester, See: Sacco and Vanzetti Correspondence No. 1 (Subject Section) // LOWELL, Robert (From Jim Peck), See: Sacco and Vanzetti Correspondence No. 3 (Subject Section) // (+)LUCHKOVSKY, Lisa (restricted use) // LUNLDELIUS, Mrs. A. // LUNDOFF, John M. // *LYLA // LYMAN, R. H. // LYONS, Eugene, See Also: Sacco and Vanzetti Correspondence No. 2 (Subject Section) // LYONS, Louis, See: Sacco and Vanzetti Correspondence No. 2 (Subject Section).
    MC________, Zack // MC ARTHUR, Fred J., See: Centralia Correspondence No. 2 (Subject Section) // McCAFFREY, Msgr. Joseph J. // McDONALD, Lucy, See: Centralia Correspondence No. 1 (Subject Section) // McFEE, William // McGILL, Andrew (Pseudonym), See: MORLEY, Christopher // McGIVNEY, John, See: Centralia Correspondence No. I (Subject Section) // McGURRIN, Hon. James // McINTYRE, 0. 0. // McLEAN, Alex, See: Centralia Correspondence No. 1 (Subject Section) // McKNIGHT, Charles, See: Centralia Correspondence No. 2 (Subject Section) // McNAMARA, Hon. Edmund L., See: Sacco and Vanzetti Correspondence No. 3 (Subject Section) // *MC SWIGAN, Marie //
    *MAHLER, Herbert (Obituaries), See Also: Kentucky Miners Defense Correspondence (Subject Section) // MARER, Nat, See: League for Mutual Aid 1960s and Anniversary Dinner; Ferrer School (Subject Section) // MARI // MARIAN // MARKS, A. J. // MARTEL, Frank X., See: Centralia Correspondence No. 1 (Subject Section) // MARTIN, Alberto // MARTIN, Anna // MARTIN, Pete // MARY // MARY AND NELL (Curry family? Relatives of Beffel) // MATTHEWS, Ben A., See: Tresca Memorial Correspondence No. 5 (Subject Section) // MATTESON, Mrs. Lee (Re: Nell) // MAUCHENHEIM, C. Egan // MAURER, Meyer Emil, See: Terzani Case Correspondence (Subject Section) // MAURICE // MAY (Diana Truesdale?) // MAYNARD, Allen, See: Centralia Correspondence No. 2 (Subject Section) // MAYNARD, Louis R., See: Centralia Correspondence No. 2 (Subject Section) // MEAD, Dr. Kate Campbell Hurd // MEAGAN (Meager?), Anna // MEITLEIN, Beatrice // MEITLEIN, Rose // MELTZER, Joseph, See: Memorial Issue of Controcorrente General Correspondence (Subject Section) // *MENCKEN, H. L. // MERLING, Sam, See: Centralia Correspondence No. 2 (Subject Section) // MICHENER, Jean Duval (Mrs. A. H.) // MILGRAM, Morris // MILHOLLAND, Mrs. John E. (Including a letter to Jane Burr re: Milholland) // MILLER, G. E., See: FRESCO, Mauricio // MILLET, Pauline // MILLIGAN, Carl G. // MINA // MINGANA, A. // MINOR, Robert // MIRAVITELLES, Jaume, See: Tresca Memorial Committee No. 4 (Subject Section) // MITCHELL, Gordon, See: League for Mutual Aid 1930s (Subject Section) // MODESTO, Zapata // MOFFAT, Alexander J. // MOLISANI, E. Howard, See: Sacco and Vanzetti Correspondence No. 3 (Subject Section) // MOLONEY, Francis X. // MONTANA, Vanni, See: Tresca Memorial Committee No. 5 (Subject Section) // *MOONEY, TOM (Including two letters from Rena Mooney) // MONOLDI, P.? (Peo) // MOORE, Fred H. // MOORE, Lola D. // MOORE, Rob // MOORE, U. G., See: Centralia Correspondence No. 2 (Subject Section) // MORAN, T. J., See: Centralia Correspondence No. 2 (Subject Section) // MOREHOUSE, D. F. // MORGAN, T. S. // MORLEY, Christopher (Including a letter from Herman Abromson) // MORO, Guilio de // MOUDY, Mr. W.F., See: Centralia Correspondence No. 2 (Subject Section) // MURRAY, Pauli, See: League for Mutual Aid 1940s (Subject Section) // MUSMANNO, Hon. Michael A., See: Memorial Issue of Controcorrente; Sacco and Vanzetti (Subject Section).
    NAELY, Marshall // *NARETTY, Vera NEFF, Fanny (Re: Earl J. Yeager) // NEARING, Scott See: League for Mutual Aid Anniversary Dinner (Subject Section) // NELSON, Louis See: Sacco and Vanzetti Correspondence No. 3 (Subject Section) // NELSON, Walter M. See: MOORE, Fred H. NICHIOLS, Esta V. (Mrs. Dudley) // NICHOLS, Dr. John H. // NIELSEN ?, Jens // NOAH, Robert M. // NOLAN, P. J. See: Centralia Correspondence No. 2 (Subject Section) // NOMAD, Max (Including an incomplete manuscript of Nomad book) // NORTHROP, Miss Agnes F. See: League for Mutual Aid 1940s (Subject Section) // *NORWOOD, Rose
    0., Jessie (Oakley) // OAKLEY ?, Jessie // ODER or ODEN, Fremont // O'DONNEL, Tom C. // *O'CONNER, Harvey // *O'CONNER, Tom // O'HARE, Frank P // O'NEILL, Eugene // ORCUTT, Jessie // OSCAR OUTTIER, Alexis
    PARKER BURNETT, Adele See: Centralia Correspondence No. 2 (Subject Section) // PARKHURST, Miss See: Box 21 Helen Parkhurst // *PESOTTA, Rose (Includes ms. of chapters from her books Days of Our Lives and ' Bread Upon the Waters) See Also: Freie Arbeiter Stimme in RE: Writing (Subject Section) // PHILLIPS, Mr. See: Terzani Case Correspondence (Subject Section) // PICK MAN, Herbert See: Box 20 Paul Crouch // PIERCE, Vivian // PITMAN, Dr. '111ason // POOLE, Ernest // PORTER ?, Adna // POUND, Roscoe // *PRICE, Burr // PRINGLE, Mr. // PROCOPIO, G. D. See: Tresca Memorial Committee No. 3 (Subject Section) // PURDELL, Dorothy (Co signed with Klinger) // PUTNAM, Jim
    QUAM, S. V. ? // QUINTILIANO, Luigi See:Memorial Issue of Controcorrente General Correspondence (Subject Section)
    R., M. // R., Virginia // RAINER, Dachine // RANSDELL, Miss See: Sacco and Vanzetti Correspondence No. 1 (Subject Section) // RANDOLPTI, A. Philip See: Sacco and Vanzetti Correspondence No. 3 (Subject Section) READ, Cliff REELY, Mary K. REESE, Henry See: Tresca Memorial Committee No. 3 (Subject Section) // REGAN ?, John // REID, Ed See: Tresca Memorial Committee No. 4 (Subject Section) // REICHNER, Frieda REINEMANN, Dr. Herbert // REUTHER, Victor See: Sacco and Vanzetti Correspondence No.3 (Subject Section) // RICHMOND, Mary E. // ROBERTSON, Sue J. // ROCKER, Rudolf See: Box 23 Maximoff/Bakunin manuscript. // ROGERS, Louise // ROHAN., Jack // ROHMAN ?, Dick // ROSE // *ROY, Anna (Including an incomplete manuscript on Gandhi) // RUDOME, Jack // RUGEN, Paul See: Sacco and Vanzetti Correspondence No. 2 (Subject Section) // RUSSELL, Charles Edward // RUSSELL, Isaac K. // RYAN, William F.
    S., Bettina (Betty ?) // S., Laura // SAMUEL, Howard See: Sacco and Vanzetti Correspondence No. 3 (Subject Section) // *SANDBURG, Carl (Including one letter from Margaret Sandburg and some printed poems) // SCHALL, Hon. Thomas D. // SCHOULTZ ?, Marjorie // SCHNEIDER, Otto J. // SECO, Lawrence See: Spanish Anti Fascist Committee (Subject Section) // SECO, Nina // SELDES, George // SELTZER, Thomas // SHAPIRO, Morris See: Terzani Case Correspondence (Subject Section) // *SHEEHAN, Bill and Lucy // SHEEKS, Judge Ben // *SHIELDS, Art and Ester // *SULKIND, Adelaide (Frank) See Also: League for Mutual Aid (Subject Section) // SHUSKIE, John // SIMON, S. Fanny // *SINCLAIR, Upton // SMITH, Britt See: Centralia Correspondence No. 1 (Subject Section) // SMITH C. S. See: Centralia Correspondence No. 2 (Subject Section) // SMITH, Elmer S. See: Centralia Correspondence Nos. 1 and 2 (Subject Section) // SMITH, Harry // SMITH, Katherine // SNYDER, Edgar C. See Also: Centralia Correspondence No. 2 (Subject Section) // SOBELL, Helen (Mrs. Morton) // SOLBERG, Marshall // SOLOMON, Sidney // SPAETH, Sigmund // SPANO, Michael See: Tresca Memorial Committee No. 2 (Subject Section) // SPITZNER, Rose // *SPIVAK, John L. (Jack) // STARR, Ellen Gates See: Centralia Correspondence No. 1 (Subject Section) // STARR, Frederick See: Centralia Correspondence No. 2 (Subject Section) // *STARRETT, Vincent // STARRETT, Walter See: United Libertarian Organization (Subject Section) // STARK, Louis See: Sacco and Vanzetti Correspondence No. 1 (Subject Section) // STEIMER, Molly // STEINBACH, Sophia // STEPHAN, Isabel // STONE, Irving // STRONG, Sydney // STULBERG, Louis See: Sacco and Vanzetti Correspondence No. 3 (Subject Section) // SULGROVE, Leslie B. // SUHR, Herman See: Ford and Suhr (Subject Section) // SULLIVAN ?, Frank // SULLIVAN. Timothy // SUTTON, George W. (Jr.) // SWANSON, Dorothy // SWEET, Coleman C. (With note on back from Homer Croy) // SYMIES, Lillian